const questions = [
    {
        question: "On what day of the year is The Little Match Girl set?",
        optionA: "On Christmas day",
        optionB: "On Last evening of the year",
        optionC: "On Easter",
        optionD: "On Good Friday",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },

    {
        question: "The poor little girl was ____ and ____.",
        optionA: "sick and weak",
        optionB: "well-dressed and dazzling",
        optionC: "bare head and naked feet",
        optionD: "happy and cheerful",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "The story is narrated from a ____ omniscient perspective.",
        optionA: "second person",
        optionB: "third person",
        optionC: "first person",
        optionD: "fourth person",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },

    {
        question: "The story propagates the idea that ____ are necessary to remain happy, even if for a short while.",
        optionA: "money",
        optionB: "friends",
        optionC: "dreams",
        optionD: "wishes",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "The author give us a glimpse into the ____ society.",
        optionA: "English",
        optionB: "Elizabethan",
        optionC: "Victorian",
        optionD: "Modern",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "She carried a number of	matches in her old ____.",
        optionA: "dress",
        optionB: "apron",
        optionC: "tunic",
        optionD: "frock",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },

    {
        question: "The images seen by the girl were fragments ____.",
        optionA: "of her dreams",
        optionB: "of her hope",
        optionC: "of her unfulfilled desires",
        optionD: "of her fears",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "She could not earn anything because ____.",
        optionA: "Noone	had	bought anything	of her the whole day.",
        optionB: "Noone had	given her even a penny.",
        optionC: "Both A and B",
        optionD: "Noone had anything",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "How did she try to keep herself warm?",
        optionA: "by pulling her apron closer",
        optionB: "by rubbing her hands",
        optionC: "by burning the matches",
        optionD: "by turning on the heater",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "The shooting star is foreshadowing ____.",
        optionA: "Her sadness",
        optionB: "Her death",
        optionC: "Her misery",
        optionD: "Her happiness",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },

    {
        question: "The vision that the little match girl saw when she lit the first match was of ____.",
        optionA: "an iron stove",
        optionB: "a beautiful Christmas tree",
        optionC: "a delicious meal laid out on a table",
        optionD: "her beautiful grandmother",
        correctOption: "optionA"
    },

    {
        question: "When the little girl strikes her second match, the light burns brightly, turning the wall beside 'transparent like a thin veil.'Â What is the figure of speech?",
        optionA: "Metaphor",
        optionB: "Simile",
        optionC: "Personification",
        optionD: "Oxymoron",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },


    {
        question: "Matches symbolise ______.",
        optionA: "Joy",
        optionB: "Light",
        optionC: "Hope",
        optionD: "Pain",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },


    {
        question: "The little match girl who died of _____.",
        optionA: "cold and starvation",
        optionB: "sorrow and gloom",
        optionC: "misery and sickness",
        optionD: "heat and starvation",
        correctOption: "optionA"
    },

    {
        question: "The last image, the vision of ______, was the most important to the little girl.",
        optionA: "the Christmas tree",
        optionB: "her grandmother",
        optionC: "shooting star",
        optionD: "iron stove",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    }
]
